Guide to the Samuel P. Hays Post-World War II Radical Movements Publications Collection, 1915-1982 AIS.1981.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Radical Right Publications, 1915-1978; III.
  - Libertarian American, a forum of news commentary and dialogue (San Antonio, TX), v. 1 no. 1-6, April/May, 1967-March/June 1968; v. 2 no. 1-4, Nov. 1968-Aug./Sept. 1969; June-Aug. 1970, 18.
  - Libertarian Connection (Los Angeles, CA), no. 1-3, 5-10, Dec. 10, 1968-April 13, 1969, June 29, 1969-April 26, 1970, 19.
  - Libertarian Forum (New York, NY), v. 1, Aug. 15-Dec. 15, 1969; v. 2, 1970 (lacks no. 17, Sept. 1); v. 3 no. 2, Feb. 1971, 20.
  - Libertarian Iconoclast (Berkeley, CA), v. 3 no. 2, Dec. 1968, 21.
  - Libertarian Review (Landover Hills, MD), v. 5 no. 2, March/April 1976, 22.
  - Liberty League News (New Salem, ND), v. 1 no. 8, May 28, 1959; v. 2 no. 1, 4, Jan., Dec., 1961; v. 3 no. 2, July 1962; v. 4 no. 1, March 1963; v. 5 no. 2, March 1964; v. 6 no. 1, Jan. 1965, 23.
  - Liberty Ledger (Washington, DC), 1969, 24.
  - Liberty Letter (Washington, DC), no. 49-62, Jan. 1965-March 1966; no. 69, Oct. 1966; no. 71-100, Dec. 1966-June 1964; no. 102-142, Aug. 1969-Feb. 1973; no. 144-161, April 1973-Sept. 1974; no. 172, Aug. 1975, 25.
  - Liberty Lobby (Washington, DC), April-July 1970, 26.
  - Liberty Lowdown (Washington, DC), no. 74-76, April-June, 1969; no. 79-80, Sept.-Oct., 1969; no. 82-91, Dec. 1969-Sept. 1970; no. 93-97, Nov. 1970-March 1971; no. 107, 114, March, Dec. 1972, 27.
  - Life in America (Washington, DC), April-July/Aug. 1971, 1. (Box 65)
  - Life Line Freedom Talk (Washington, DC: Life Line Foundation), Aug. 14-Dec. 31, 1966; 1967; Jan. 1-Sept. 13, 1968, 2.
  - Life Lines (Washington, DC: Life Line Foundation), v. 8 no. 97-156, Aug. 15-Dec. 30, 1966; v. 9 no. 1-100, 102-138, 147-156, Jan.-Aug. 21, Aug. 25-Nov. 17, Dec. 8-29, 1967; v. 10, 1968; v. 11 no. 1-27, 40-156, Jan. 3-March 5, April 4-Dec. 1969; v. 12 no. 1-77, 92, Jan. 2-July 1, Aug. 5, 1970, 3.
  - Life Span (St. Petersburg, FL), Fall 1965, 1. (Box 66)
  - Los Angeles Daily Bulletin (Los Angeles, CA), v. 1 no. 1-48, May 15-July 30, 1952, 2.
  - Louisiana Eagle (New Orleans, LA), v. 1 no. 1, Oct. 1969, 3.
  - Loyal American (Muskegon, MI), July 29, 1969, 4.
  - Man and State: a Student Conservative Journal, v. 3, no. 1, Dec. 1964, 5.
  - Mankind Quarterly (Edinburgh, Scotland), v. 2-10, 1961/1962-1970/1971, 6.
  - Manion Forum (South Bend, IN), no. 483-831, 1964-Sept. 1970, 7.
  - Manion Forum Newsletter (South Bend, IN), v. 6 no. 15-v. 10 no. 17, 1966-1970, 8.
  - Michigan School Observer (Lansing, MI: The Friends of Michigan Schools), v. 7 no. 3-12, 1967; v. 8 no. 7-8, 1968; v. 9 no. 1, 1969, 9.
  - Midnight Cry Messenger (Southern Pines, NC: Bible Tabernacle of Southern Pines), v. 8, no. 2, March/April 1964; v. 9, no. 2, 6, March/April, Nov./Dec. 1965; v. 10, no. 2-4, May-Oct. 1966, 10.
  - Mindszenty Report (St. Louis, MO: The Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation),1964-1970, 11.
  - Minute Women (Wheeling, WV), no. 4, 10-93, 1955-1966, 12.
  - Modern Viking ( El Monte, CA: Western Division, National Socialist White People's Party), no. 1, July 1968, 13.
  - Miss Kassel Says (Fort Worth, TX), v. 1-5, 1965-1970, 14.
  - National Christian News (St. Petersburg, FL: National Christian Publishers), v. 4 no. 1-5, 1966; v. 5 no. 1-3, 1967; v. 7, 1968; v. 8 no. 1-3, 1969, 15.
  - Modern Age (Chicago, IL), v. 7 no. 3, 4, 1963; v. 8-25, 1966-1981, 1. (Box 67)
  - National Chronicle (Burney, CA), v. 15 no. 22-29, 38-52, 1966; v. 16 no. 42-51, 1967; v. 17-18, 1968-1969; v. 19 no. 4-52, 1970; v. 20 no. 1-19, Jan. 21-June 3, 1971, 1. (Box 68)
  - National Decency Reporter (Cincinnati, OH: Citizens for Decent Literature), v. 3 no. 8-9, 1967, 2.
  - National Defender (Washington, DC: National Defense Committee), v. 8-10 no. 6, Sept. 1966-Feb. 1969, 3.
  - National Fluoridation News (Hempstead, Long Island, NY), v. 9 no. 2, April/May 1963; v. 17 no. 1, Jan./Feb. 1971, 4.
  - National Health Federation Bulletin (Monrovia, CA), v. 7 no. 2-3, 1961; v. 8 no. 2, 4-5, 9-12, 1962; v. 9-10, 1963-1964; v. 11 no. 2-12, 1965; v. 12 no. 11, 1966; v. 13-15, 1967-1969, 5.
  - National Laymen's Digest (Chicago, IL: Church League of America), v. 1 no. 1-16, May 1-Dec. 16, 1969; v. 2 no. 1-4, Jan. 1-Feb. 15, 1970, 6.
  - National Newsletter of Politics and Principles, and People ( Washington, DC: Constitutional Alliance, Inc.), v. 4-5, 1969-1970, 7.
  - National Program Letter (Searcy, AR: National Education Program), Feb-Dec. 1966; 1967-1975; May-Nov. 1976; Feb.-Sept., Dec. 1977; Jan. 1978-May 1981, 8.
  - National Review (Meridan, CT), v. 17 no. 44, Nov. 2, 1965; v. 18-21, 1966-1969; v. 22, odd no. 's only, 1970; v. 23, odd no. 's only, 1971, 1. (Box 69)
  - National Socialist (London, England: National Socialist Movement), no. 4, May 1963; no. 6-7, undated; no. 8-10, Jan./March 1965-Summer 1966, 1. (Box 70)
  - National Socialist World (Arlington, VA: World Union of National Socialists), no. 1-6, Spring 1966-Winter 1968, 2.
  - Nation's Press and Free China (Washington, DC), Feb., May, Aug., Nov. 1974; Feb. 1975, 3.
  - Nazi Action (Glendale, CA: American Nazi Party), v. 7 no. 2, March/April 1968, 4.
  - Nebraska Beacon (Lincoln, NE), v. 68 no. 6-12, July-Dec. 1967; v. 69, 1968; v. 70 no. 1-10, Jan.-Oct. 1969, 5.
  - New Guard (Washington, DC: Young Americans for Freedom), v. 2 no. 1-10, Jan.-Oct. 1962; v. 3 no. 3, 6-7, 9, 11, March, June-July, Sept., Nov. 1963; v. 4, 1964; v. 5 no. 7-12, July-Dec., 1965; v. 6-10 no. 11, 1966-Nov. 1970, 6.
  - New Patriot (Chicago, IL), v. no. 1, Fall 1978, 7.
  - New Patriot (Hollywood, CA), v. 8-9, 1966-1967, 8.
  - New Right (Centerline, MI: Michigan National Youth Alliance), v. 3 no. 7-8, March-Sept. 1969, 9.
  - New Right Counterthrust (Centerline, MI), v. 1 no. 5-6, June-Oct. 1968, 10.
  - New Romanticist (Kansas City, MO), v. 1 no. 4-9, July 1968-1969, 11.
  - News and Views (Wheaton, IL: National Laymen's Council of the Church League), no. 175, 177, May 31, Sept. 17, 1947; no. 197-198, Oct. 20-Dec. 1, 1949; no. 202, 204-205, 207, 1950; no. 214, July 1951; no. 219-220, 225, 228, 1952; no. 234-235, 238, 240, 1953; no. 242, 245-248, 1954; no. 258, 262-263, 1955; no. 267, 271, 275, 1956; v. 20-27, 1957-1964, 12.
  - News and Views (Wheaton, IL: National Laymen's Council of the Church League), v. 28-32, 1965-1969; v. 33 no. 1-3, Jan.-March 1970; v. 36 no. 9, Sept. 1973, 1. (Box 71)
  - News Behind the News (Ottawa, Ont.: National Federation of Christian Laymen), Supplement section, Oct. 1956; v. 1 no. 10-11, Aug.-Sept. 1957; v. 2 no. 9, July/Aug. 1958, 2.
  - News From the Free Society (Washington, DC: Free Society Association), v. 1 no. 9-10, May-Aug. 1966; v. 2 no. 1-9, Sept. 1966-Nov. 1967, 3.
  - News from Germany (Starnberg, Bavaria, Germany), no. 6, April 1940; Special edition no. 2, May 1940, 4.
  - Northern World: A Quarterly Journal of Northern European Affairs (London, England), v. 5 no. 1, 3, Autumn 1960, Spring 1961, 5.
  - Northlander: A Monthly Review of Pan Nordic Affairs (Coventry, England: The Northern League), v. 1 no. 7, Nov./Dec. 1958; v. 6 no. 5, Oct. 1963; v. 7 no. 1-5, Feb.-Oct. 1964; v. 8 no. 1, Feb. 1965, 6.
  - Northwest Defense News (Walla Walla, WA: Northwest League for Christian Americanism), v. 1 no. 3, July/Aug. 1951, 7.
  - Notes from FEE (Irvington on Hudson, NY: The Foundation for Economic Education), Nov. 1966; Jan. 1967-Feb. 1971, 8.
  - NS Bulletin (Arlington, VA), no. 50, 65, 67, 69-71, 76, 1970; no. 90, 1971, 9.
  - On Target (Brentwood, MD: The Minutemen), Aug.-Dec. 1965; Feb. 1966-May 1967; Aug.-Dec. 1971, 10.
  - On Target (Flesherton, Ont.: Canadian Intelligence Publications), no. 55-115, 130, Sept. 30 1968-Nov. 24, 1969, March 9, 1970, 11.
  - Optimate (Evanston, IL: Northwestern Young Conservative Club, Northwestern University), v. 3 no. 3, January 1965, 12.
  - Options: A Critical Review (Phoenix, MD), v. 1 no. 1-16, May 1-Dec. 15, 1969; v. 2 no. 1-20, Jan.-Oct. 15, 1970, 13.
  - Over Here: The Magazine of Higher Consciousness (Noblesville, IN), v. 2 no. 7, 9-12, July, Sept.-Dec 1958; v. 4 no. 3-11/12, March-Nov./Dec., 1960, 14.
  - Our Country (Cardinal, VA), no. 48-67, Nov. 1966-Jan. 1971, 15.
  - PCU Sentinel (Harrisburg, PA; Pennsylvania Conservative Union), v. 1 no. 1-3, May-Dec. 1970; v. 2, 1971; v. 3 no. 1-2, Jan./Feb.-June 1972; v. 4, 1973; v. 5 no. 1-3, Feb.-Sept. 1974; v. 6, 1975; v. 7 no. 1-2, Feb.-Aug. 1976; v. 8 no. 1, Jan. 1977, 16.
  - Palestine Issue (New York, NY: Palestine Liberation Organization), v. 1 no. 1-9, May 1966-May/June 1968, 17.
  - Pan American Headlines (New York, NY: Committee on Pan American Policy), v. 6 no. 2-5, July 1966-April 1967; v. 7, March 1968-Nov. 1969; v. 8, Sept. 1970-Oct. 1972; v. 9, Jan. 1973-Aug. 1974; v. 10, Nov. 1974-Nov./Dec. 1975; v. 11 no. 1-3, Feb. 1976-Oct. 1976; v. 12 no. 1-4, Jan.-July/Aug. 1977; v. 13 no. 1, 3, Jan./Feb., May/June 1978; v. 14 no. 1-4, Jan. 1979-Oct. 1979; v. 15 no. 1-4, Jan.-Oct. 1980; v. 16 no. 1, 3-4 Jan./Feb., July/Aug.-Sept./Oct. 1981; v. 17 no. 1, Jan./Feb. 1982, 18.
  - Patriot Tribune (Pineville, LA: Pineville News Co.), v. 63 no. 54-69, March 5-June 18, 1970, 19.
  - Patriotic Party Newsletter (Independence, MO), Sept. 1966; Dec. 1970; Feb., April, Dec. 1971; March 1972, 20.
  - Patriotic Preview (North Hollywood, CA), no. 39-90, Sept. 1966-Dec. 1970, 21.
  - Pelley's Weekly (Asheville, MC: The Christian Party and the Councils of Safety), v. 2 no. 7, July 1, 1936, 22.
  - Pennsylvania Constitutionalist (Harrisburg, PA: Constitutional Party), no. 1-50, Sept. 1966-Dec. 1970; no. 62, March 1972, 23.
  - Persuasion at Work (Rockford, IL), v. 1 no. 1, March 1978, 24.
  - Phyllis Schlafly Report (Alton, IL), v. 1-8, 1967/1968-1974/1975; v. 9 no. 1-5, 11-12, Aug.-Nov. 1975, June-July 1976; v. 10 no. 1-10, Aug. 1976-May 1977; v. 11 no. 1, 3-4, 8-11, Aug., Oct.-Nov. 1977, March-June 1978; v. 12 no. 2, 7-12, Sept. 1978, Feb.-July 1979; v. 13, 1979/1980; v. 14 no. 1-9, 12, Aug. 1980-April 1981, July 1981; v. 15 no. 5, Dec. 1981, 25.
  - Pilgrim Torch (Englewood, CO: Soldiers of the Cross), 1966-Fall 1967, 26.
  - Politics (Washington, DC: Constitutional Alliance), v. 4 no. 1-v. 5 no. 24, Jan. 15, 1969-Dec. 31, 1970, 1. (Box 72)
  - Price of Progress (Hansdale, IL), Aug. 1968-Sept. 1969, 2.
  - Prophetic Expositor (Toronto, Ont.: Baptist Israel World Federation, Inc.), Oct., Dec. 1966, 3.
  - Prophetic Reporter (Portland, OR), v. 6 no. 30, 33-46, undated (ca. 1965-1966); v. 7 no. 1-3, undated (ca. 1965-1966), 4.
  - Provoker (St. Catharines, Ont.), v. 7, March/April, July-Dec., 1967, 5.
  - Race (Jackson, MS: The New Patriot), v. 1 no. 1-2, 1967, 6.
  - Raise the Banner (El Monte, CA: Western Division of the American Nazi Party), 1 issue, undated (ca. 1967), 7.
  - Western Division Bulletin (El Monte, CA: Western Division of the American Nazi Party), no. 1-2, April-May, 1968, 8.
  - Rally (Wauwatosa, WI), v. 1, June 1966-May 1967; v. 2, no. 1-5, June-Nov. 1967, 9.
  - Rampart College Newsletter (Larkspur, CO; Santa Ana, CA), v. 3 no. 2-12, Feb.-Dec. 1966; v. 4 1967; v. 5 no. 1-9, Jan.-Sept. 1968; n.s. v. 1 no. 5, May 1971; n. s. v. 2 no. 1 4, 6, 9, 10, Jan.-Spring, June, Sept., Oct. 1972, 10.
  - Rampart Journal (Boulder, CO), v. 1-4, 1965-1968, 11.
  - Rational Individualist (Silver Springs, MD: Society for Rational Individualism), v. 1 no. 2, 4-6, 9-13, Jan.-April, July-Nov., 1969, 12.
  - Reason, A Review of Politics (Fullerton, CA), v. 1 no. 2-3, April-May, 1965, 13.
  - Report on Freedom (Los Angeles: CA: Liberty Amendment Committee of the U.S.A.), v. 1 no. 10-11, April-June, 1966; v. 2 no. 1-4, Aug. 1966-May 1967; v. 3 no. 1-3, July-Nov. 1967; v. 4, 1968; v. 5, no. 1-4, Feb.-Oct., 1969; v. 6, 1970; v. 7 no. 1, April, 1971, 14.
  - Report to America (Washington, DC: American Coalition of Patriotic Societies), v. 6- 8 no. 4, Jan. 1965-April 1967, 15.
  - Revere: Alerting America (Hinsdale, IL), v. 2 no. 16, Nov. 1956; v. 4 no. 9, Sept. 1958, 16.
  - Review of the News (Belmont, MA: Correction, Please!), v. 1 no. 14-17, Dec. 1965; v. 2, 1966 (lacks no. 43, Nov. 2); v. 3-5, 1967-1969; v. 6 no. 1-8, Jan.-Feb. 1970, 1. (Box 73)
  - Right (San Francisco, CA), no. 1-60, Oct. 1955-Sept. 1960, 1. (Box 74)
  - Rockwell Report (Dallas, TX: National Socialist White People's Party, American Nazi Party), Oct. 1964; July 1965; June-Dec. 1966; Feb.-March, June 1967, 2.
  - Roll Call, "The Voice of the Loyal Opposition" (Indianapolis, IN: Fellowship Press, Inc.), v. 1 no. 22-23, June 9-16, 1941; v. 2 no. 3, 5, 10-11, 15-20, July 27-Dec. 1, 1941, 3.
  - SIL News (Philadelphia, PA: Society for Individual Liberty), v. 1 no. 1, 3-9, Jan.-Nov. 1970, 4.
  - SIL Service Bulletin (Philadelphia, PA: Society for Individual Liberty), 1970-1972, 5.
  - St. Michael's News (Zarephath, NJ: St. Michael's Legions for the Preservation of Christianity), v. 2 no. 5-7, 12, Sept-Nov. 1968, April 1969, 6.
  - St. Michael's Newsletter (Orange, CA: St. Michael's Seminary and Novitiate), v. 7 no. 1-5, Feb.-Nov. 1968; v. 8 no. 1-4, March-July 1969; v. 9 no. 1-5, Jan.-Sept. 1970; v. 10 no. 1-4, Feb.-Oct. 1971; v. 11 no. 1-4, Jan.-July 1972; v. 12 no. 3, June 1973; v. 13 no. 1-4, Jan-Aug. 1974; v. 14 no. 1, 3, Feb., Sept. 1975; v. 15 no. 1-3, Jan.-June 1976, 7.
  - Sandtown Story (Atlanta, GA), Bulletin no. 38-98, May 1962-Dec. 1967, 8.
  - Seventh Trumpet (Dallas, TX), July 1962-Oct. 1967; 1968-1970 (lacks Oct.1969), 9.
  - Severance Voice (Saginaw, MI), no. 1-13, Dec. 1958-Jan./Sept. 1961, 10.
  - Silver Ranger (Los Angeles, CA: The Silver Legion, Pacific Division), v. 3 no. 8, 12-15, 17, Jan. 17-March 21, 1934, 11.
  - Situationist International (New York, NY), no. 1, June 1969, 12.
  - Social Credit (Walters Falls, Ont.: Canadian Credit Movement), v. 2 no. 3-9, June-Dec. 1980, 13.
  - Sons of Liberty Newsletter (Hollywood, GA), June-Dec. 1969; Jan.-March 1970, 14.
  - Sons of the American Revolution Magazine (Washington, DC: Sons of the American Revolution), v. 61, no. 2, Oct. 1966, 15.
  - Source (New York, NY), v. 2 no. 1, Fall 1967, 16.
  - South: The News Magazine of Dixie (Auburn, AL), v. 31 no. 6-7, June-July 1966, 17.
  - Southern Conservative (Lexington, VA: Unincorporated Association of Students at Washington and Lee University), v. 4 no. 3, Feb. 1965, 18.
  - Southern Review (Jackson, MS), v. 2 no. 7-9, 11-24, July 1/15-Aug. 1, Aug. 15, 1966-March 1, 1967; v. 3 no. 1-11, March 15-Aug. 15, 1967; v. 4 no. 1-10, 14-16, Feb.-Aug. 12, Nov. 4-Dec. 16, 1968; v. 5 no. 1-11, Jan.-Aug. 6, 1969, 19.
  - Spearhead (London, England: Greater Britain Movement), Dec. 1964; Feb.-March, May 1965, 20.
  - Special Office Brief (Dublin, Ireland), n.s. no. 152, May 18, 1979, 21.
  - National Spotlight (Washington, DC), v. 1 no. 1-3, Sept. 17-Oct. 1, 1975, 22.
  - Spotlight (Washington, DC), v. 2 no. 22-41, 43-52, May 31-Oct. 1, Oct. 25-Dec. 27, 1976; v. 3 no. 1-12, 38, Jan. 3-March 21, Sept. 19, 1977, 23.
  - Statecraft: A Journal of Political Education (Center Line, MI: National Youth Alliance), v. 1 no. 1-3, Sept.-Dec. 1968; v. 2 no. 1-4, Jan.-Aug. 1969; v. 3 no. 1-3, 1970; v. 4, Jan. 1972, 1. (Box 75)
  - Statecraft Report (Somerset, NJ), v. 1 no. 2, May 1971, 2.
  - Storm Trooper (Arlington, VA: American Nazi Party), Summer, Winter 1965; Spring 1966, 3.
  - Success (Grand Rapids, MI: Constitutional Alliance), v. 1 no. 1-2, 9-12, Jan.-April, July-Oct. 1966; v. 2 no. 1-12, Nov. 1966-Oct. 1967; v. 3 no. 1-7, 9-25, Nov. 1967-Dec. 1968, 4.
  - Tactics, Anti Communist Liaison (Arlington, VA), v. 1-5, 1964-1968; v. 6 no. 1, Jan. 20, 1969, 5.
  - Tanstaafl (Philadelphia, PA), Spring 1969, 6.
  - Task Force (Annandale, VA: Defenders of the American Constitution, Inc.), v. 13-16, 1966-1969; v. 17 no. 1-9, 1970, 7.
  - Tax Fax (New Orleans, LA), no. 12-13, 15, 26-29, 31, 33-35, 37, 39, 42-43, 45-51, 55-113, 116-117, 119-120, 1959-1972, 8.
  - Tax Report (Los Angeles, CA), 1967, 9.
  - Textbook Evaluation Report (New Rochelle, NY: America's Future Textbook Evaluation Committee), 1950-1964, 10.
  - Threefold (New York, NY), 1949-1963, 11.
  - Thunderbolt (Savannah, GA: National States Right Party), no. 51-158, May 1963-March 1973; no. 164, 166, Sept., Nov. 1973, 12.
  - Times of the Americas (Miami, FL), v. 9 no. 6-13, 1965; v. 10 no. 1-46, 1966; v. 11 no. 1-13, 1967, 13.
  - Tocsin (Davis, CA), v. 7 no. 11-19, 1966; v. 8 no. 1-8, 1967, 14.
  - Treason Series (Hamilton, MT: The Revere Press), v. 1, 1968, 1. (Box 76)
  - Tribune of Enslaved Nations (Salem, MA), no. 83/10, Oct. 1963; no. 85/12, Dec. 1963; no. 98/2-99/3, Feb./March 1976; no. 101/5, May 1965; no. 102/6, June 1965; no. 109/1, Jan. 1966, 2.
  - Trud (Essex Falls, NJ), v. 1 no. 6-14, 1969; v. 2 no. 1, 34-38, 1970, 3.
  - True News: America's Family Picture-News Magazine (Des Moines, IA), v. 1, no. 11-12, Nov.-Dec. 1966; v. 2, 1967; v. 3, no. 1-3, Jan.-March 1968, 4.
  - Truth About Communism (New York, NY), no. 36-45, 1968-1973, 5.
  - Truth Crusader (Harrisonburg, VA), no. 20-38, Summer 1966-Spring 1971, 6.
  - Truth Forum (Pasadena, CA), April 1967-March 1971, 7.
  - Truth Seeker (San Diego, CA), v. 91 no. 12, 1964; v. 92-97 no. 4, 1965-1970, 8.
  - U.S.A. (New York, NY), v. 12 no. 22/23, Oct./Nov. 1965; Oct. 25-Dec. 1968; Jan. 1969-Feb. 1970, 9.
  - Ukrainian Quarterly (New York, NY), v. 22 no. 1, Spring 1968, 10.
  - University Bookman (New York, NY), 1966; Winter 1967; Autumn 1968; 1969-1971, 11.
  - Valor, The Golden Times Weekly (Noblesville, IN), v. 1 no. 3-4, 1950; v. 4 no. 3-5, 1952; v. 5 no. 3, 1953; v. 6 no. 3, 5- 6, 9, 12, 15, 1954; v. 7 no. 5-10, 19-21, May 29-July 3, Sept. 4-18, 1954; v. 9 no. 10, 19-21, 23, July 1955, Feb.-June, Aug. 1956; v. 10 no. 10-12, Sept.-Nov. 1957; v. 11 no. 2-10, 12, Jan.-June 1958; Jan.-March, May 1959; v. 12 no. 2, July 1959; v. 13 no. 8, 10-11, Jan., March-April 1960; v. 14 no. 1-3, July-Dec. 1961, 12.
  - Viking Age (Tillson, NY: Odinist and Nordic Faith Movement), no. 1-5, Oct./Nov. 1964-April/May 1965, 13.
  - Virginian (Highland Springs, VA: Virginia League), v. 1 no. 1-6, July-Dec. 1955; v. 2 no. 1-3, 6-7, 10, 12, Jan.-April, June-July, Oct., Dec. 1966; v. 3 no. 1, 3-4, 6 -11, Jan., March-April, June-Dec. 1967/Jan. 1958; v. 4 no. 1-2, Jan.-Feb., 1958, 14.
  - Voice of the Federation (Brooklyn, NY: American Citizens of German Descent in the U.S.A.), v. 16 no. 3, 5-9, May, Sept. 1966-Jan. 1967; v. 17-20, 1967/1968-1970/1971; v. 21 no. 1-9, March 1971-Jan. 1972, 15.
  - Voice of Liberty (Decatur, GA), v. 6 no. 2, Fall 1966; v. 7 no. 1, Fall 1967; v. 8 no. 1-2, Fall-Winter 1968; v. 9 no. 1, Fall 1969; v. 10 no. 1, Fall 1970; v. 11 no. 1, Spring 1971; v. 12 no. 1, Fall 1972; v. 13 no. 1-3, March-Fall 1973; v. 14 no. 1, 3, Jan., Sept. 1974, 16.
  - Volition: a Libertarian Review (Washington, DC), v. 1 no. 1-3, Feb.-April/June 1969, 17.
  - WYCF Report (New York, NY: World Youth Crusade for Freedom), v. 1 no. 1-2, July-Nov., 1966, 1. (Box 77)
  - Washington Intelligence Report (Washington, DC: United States Anti Communist Congress), v. 1-2, 1968-1969; v. 3 no. 1-7, 9-11, Jan.-July, Sept.-Nov. 1970; v. 4, 1971; v. 5 no. 1-3, Jan./Feb.- May/June 1972, 2.
  - Washington Observer ( Washington, DC), no. 20-98, Jan. 15, 1966-May 1 1970; no. 102A, Aug. 2, 1970; no. 168-175, Jan. 1-15, 1974; no. 189, Nov. 15, 1974; no. 196-202, 211, April 1-May 15, July 1, 1975, 3.
  - Washington Report (Chicago, IL: American Security Council), W.R. 64-14, April 13, 1964; W.R. 65-1, 65-4, 65-5, Jan. 4, 25, Feb. 3, 1965; W.R. 66-13, April 4, 1966;W.R. 69-29, July 28, 1969; W.R. 69-32--W.R. 70-23, Aug. 18, 1969-Dec. 21, 1970, 4.
  - Watch Washington (New Orleans, LA), v. 1 no. 1-7, Feb. 5-Oct. 10, 1969; v. 2 no. 1, Jan. 26, 1970, 5.
  - Weekly Crusader (Tulsa, OK: Christian Crusade), v. 1, Oct. 1960-Oct. 1961; v. 3 no. 7, 9-10, 28, 46, 50-51, 1963; v. 4 no. 7-9, 11-22, 25-26, 28-32, 37-40, 42-44, 46-52, 1964, 6.
  - Western Destiny (Los Angeles, CA), v. 9 no. 6-12, June-Dec. 1964; v. 10, 1965; v. 11, no. 1-4, Jan. April 1966, 1. (Box 78)
  - Western Front (Hollywood, CA), no. 10-65, undated, 2.
  - Western Patriot (Santa Ana, CA: The Patriotic Party), v. 1 no. 1-2, Jan.-Feb. 1964, 3.
  - Western World Review (Culver City, CA), v. 3 no. 3-4, Fall 1968-Winter 1968/1969; v. 5 no. 2-3, Fall 1970-Winter 1970/1971; v. 6 no. 3, Fall 1971, 4.
  - Western World Review Newsletter (Culver City, CA), no. 8, March 1971, 5.
  - White American (Birmingham, AL: National White Americans Party), April-Oct. 1964; March, Sept.-Oct. 1965; June 1966, 6.
  - White Power (Arlington, VA), no. 7-45, Nov. 1973; no. 59, Jan. 1975; no. 97, Jan./Feb. 1981, 7.
  - White Sentinel (Ft. Lauderdale, FL: Christian Constitutional Education League), v. 16 no. 7-11, 1966; v. 17-18 no. 4, 1967-1968, 8.
  - White World (Washington, DC: White Party of America), v. 3, no. 1, 9-10, Jan., Sept.-Oct. 1967, 9.
  - Williams Intelligence Summary (Hollywood, CA), v. 1 no. 1-2, 4-12, Dec. 1948-Jan., March-Nov. 1949; v. 2-3, Dec. 1949-Nov. 1951; v. 4 no. 1-10, 12, Dec. 1951-Sept., Nov. 1952; v. 5 no. 1-2, Dec. 1952-Nov. 1953; v. 6 no. 1-2, 4-5-7-9, 11-12, Dec. 1953-Jan. 1954, March-April, June-Aug., Oct.-Nov. 1954; v. 7 no. 2-12, Jan.-Nov. 1955; v. 8 no. 1-12, Dec. 1955-Nov. 1956; v. 9 no. 1-2, 4-7, 9-12, Dec. 1956-Jan. 1957, March-June, Aug.-Nov. 1957; v. 10 no. 1-4, Dec. 1957-March 1958, 10.
  - Winrod Letter (Gainsville, MO), no. 60-98, 1967-1970; no. 148, Jan. 1975, 11.
  - Wire Magazine: Communism is Treason (Buffalo, NY: D. L. Jackson), Dec. 1966; v. 4, March-Oct. 1968; v. 5, Jan./April 1969; v. 7, March-July 1970; v. 8, Aug.-Dec. 1970, 12.
  - Woman Constitutionalist (Summit, MS: Women for Constitutional Government), v. 1-9, Sept. 1964-May 1973, 13.
  - Women's Voice (Chicago, IL), v. 5 no. 2, 1946; v. 6 no. 4, 1947; v. 7 no. 3, 8, 1948; v. 9 no. 9-10, 1951; v. 10-22, 1951/1952-1961/1962, 14.
  - YAF Letter (Washington, DC), 1 issue, undated, 15.
  - Yale Republican (New Haven, CT), Feb. 1965, 16.
  - Young Americans (Washington, DC), v. 1 no. 4, 1967, 17.
  - Young Americans Action Line (Washington, DC: Young Americans for Freedom), Jan.-July 1969, 18.
  - Young Americans for Freedom (Pittsburgh, PA: Western Pennsylvania Council), no. 1-11, Aug. 1966-June 1967, 19.
  - Young Republican Outlook (San Bernadino, CA), March 1968, 20.
- Radical Left Publications, 1949-1982; IV.
  This series consists of titles expressing views from the far left of the political spectrum. While most were published in the United States, there are a number of titles from Canada and Europe. These publications deal with issues such as the Vietnam War, civil rights, socialism and communism, and are arranged alphabetically by title.
  - ACEN News (New York, NY: Assembly of Captive European Nations), no. 122-153, March/April 1966-Nov./Dec. 1971; Special issue, Nov. 1967, 1. (Box 79)
  - ADL Bulletin (New York, NY: Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith), v. 20 no. 5, 6-10, May, Sept.-Dec. 1963; v. 21-23, 1964-1966; v. 24, 1967 (lacks May, Dec.); v. 25 no. 3, 6, March, June 1968, 2.
  - AIM, Bulletin of the American Independent Movement (New Haven, CT: Independent Political Action Committee), v. 1, 1966/67 (lacks no. 2, 12); v. 2 no. 1-13, 1967/68; v. 3, 1968/69 (lacks no. 1, 9); v. 4, 1969; v. 5 no. 1, Jan. 1970, 3.
  - A Way Out (Brookville, OH: School of Living), v. 23 no. 3-5, Sept.-Oct. 1967, 4.
  - Action for Freedom (London, England), Autumn 1969, 5.
  - Activist (Oberlin, OH), no. 20-36, Fall 1967-Spring 1975, 6.
  - Ad Hoc Bulletin (Chicago, IL: Ad Hoc Committee for a Marxist Leninist Party U.S.A.), v. 5 no. 4-7, June-Nov. 1967; v. 6 no. 1-4, 6, Jan.-May, July-Aug., Dec. 1968; v. 7 no. 1-4, Feb.-Sept., 1969; v. 8 no. 1-3, Jan.-Sept., 1970; v. 9 no. 1-2, April-Sept., 1971; v. 10 no. 1-2, June-Oct.,1972, 7.